[{"answer": "Well, I don't know.", "docId": "120813pmt", "aSentId": 45, "question": "Who has the thickest skin, you or the rhino?", "qSentId": 44}, {"answer": "INGRICH: I don't know, but I thought it was a very good sign.", "docId": "120813pmt", "aSentId": 56, "question": "How long is that going to last, do you think?", "qSentId": 55}, {"answer": "But -- well, but the current Ryan plan, which he developed with Senator Ron Wyden, a Democrat, the only bipartisan plan to save Medicare.", "docId": "120813pmt", "aSentId": 81, "question": "-- it is a -- it is a radical -- but it is a radical form of social engineering, isn't it?", "qSentId": 80}, {"answer": "Well, first of all, I would encourage everybody who's concerned about Catholic social doctrine to read Paul Ryan's remarkable speech at Georgetown in which he outlines his commitment to precisely the concerns of the church and helping the poor.", "docId": "120813pmt", "aSentId": 104, "question": "As a Catholic, what is your reaction?", "qSentId": 103}, {"answer": "Wait -- wait a second, Piers.", "docId": "120813pmt", "aSentId": 153, "question": "How would you describe that?", "qSentId": 152}, {"answer": "Ronald Reagan had a deeper recession under Jimmy Carter and Ronald Reagan recovered in three years.", "docId": "120813pmt", "aSentId": 165, "question": "No?", "qSentId": 164}, {"answer": "AWLENTY: I think it's a terrific pick.", "docId": "120813pmt", "aSentId": 188, "question": "And I guess more importantly, what do you think about the guy who did get the gig?", "qSentId": 187}, {"answer": "Well, Governor Romney has committed to release two years of tax returns.", "docId": "120813pmt", "aSentId": 197, "question": "When you are being vetted, I mean -- how many years back do you have to go in the vetting process?", "qSentId": 196}, {"answer": "I think his position's very reasonable, Piers, for this.", "docId": "120813pmt", "aSentId": 203, "question": "I mean unless you've got something to hide, why wouldn't you?", "qSentId": 202}, {"answer": "Well, Governor Romney has said he's going to have his own plan and does have his own plan.", "docId": "120813pmt", "aSentId": 217, "question": "If you were a guessing man, what percentage of the Ryan budget plan could you envisage a Romney presidency actually adopting?", "qSentId": 216}, {"answer": "You just don't quit.", "docId": "120813pmt", "aSentId": 242, "question": "Secretary of state maybe?", "qSentId": 241}, {"answer": "Well, clearly, Piers, he's energizing the Republican Tea Party base.", "docId": "120813pmt", "aSentId": 272, "question": "But what is the Democrat view of the hyperbole that's now surrounding this guy?", "qSentId": 271}, {"answer": "Well, there is.", "docId": "120813pmt", "aSentId": 283, "question": "There's now a clear ideological difference for American people to vote on come November, isn't there?", "qSentId": 282}, {"answer": "Well, Piers, I think they should first go and look at the plan and they should also look at the Democratic budget committee analysis of the plan.", "docId": "120813pmt", "aSentId": 300, "question": "How does the American voter cut through all this and actually come to a clear verdict on this plan, giving that he's now going to be the VP running mate?", "qSentId": 299}, {"answer": "Well, absolutely.", "docId": "120813pmt", "aSentId": 320, "question": "It's just how we get there, right?", "qSentId": 319}, {"answer": "Well, I think there's some of that.", "docId": "120813pmt", "aSentId": 339, "question": "Was I reading the ruins correctly?", "qSentId": 338}, {"answer": "Welcome, sir.", "docId": "120813pmt", "aSentId": 402, "question": "How you doing?", "qSentId": 401}, {"answer": "It's taken me nearly two years.", "docId": "120813pmt", "aSentId": 404, "question": "You finally got me, huh?", "qSentId": 403}, {"answer": "I think that it's that whole thing, one step forward, one step back.", "docId": "120813pmt", "aSentId": 452, "question": "-- than it has been, 20 years ago, in your experience, since you began making movies?", "qSentId": 451}, {"answer": "I said people thought he was Jesus.", "docId": "120813pmt", "aSentId": 475, "question": "What did you say?", "qSentId": 474}, {"answer": "The bottom line is economics.", "docId": "120813pmt", "aSentId": 497, "question": "Where do you think if he gets re-elected he should push harder?", "qSentId": 496}, {"answer": "Say it again.", "docId": "120813pmt", "aSentId": 534, "question": "Did you like the Olympics?", "qSentId": 533}, {"answer": "Oh, yeah.", "docId": "120813pmt", "aSentId": 536, "question": "Did you like the Olympics?", "qSentId": 535}, {"answer": "I do.", "docId": "120813pmt", "aSentId": 538, "question": "You don't see I'm wearing my jacket?", "qSentId": 537}, {"answer": "You guys did great.", "docId": "120813pmt", "aSentId": 544, "question": "Wasn't bad, was it?", "qSentId": 543}, {"answer": "I like to say, first of all, African-Americans alone did not elect President Obama.", "docId": "120813pmt", "aSentId": 549, "question": "But has it made America more or less racist?", "qSentId": 548}, {"answer": "It was down in Texas I think.", "docId": "120813pmt", "aSentId": 566, "question": "Where?", "qSentId": 565}, {"answer": "This is the point I make.", "docId": "120813pmt", "aSentId": 575, "question": "How many people die of gunshots in England every year?", "qSentId": 574}, {"answer": "There were never red flags.", "docId": "120813pmt", "aSentId": 587, "question": "The guy from Aurora, how can you buy that much ammunition on the Internet and that's not a red flag?", "qSentId": 586}, {"answer": "They got the -- the Vulcan death grip.", "docId": "120813pmt", "aSentId": 598, "question": "Well what do you do about NRA, which holds this incredible power?", "qSentId": 597}, {"answer": "I think they both should.", "docId": "120813pmt", "aSentId": 604, "question": "Should -- should Barack Obama, rather than just talk in this kind of slightly rhetoric way, as he does about guns, should he now push?", "qSentId": 603}, {"answer": "I'm over it now, but I -- it came out of nowhere.", "docId": "120813pmt", "aSentId": 652, "question": "And then gone, how do you feel about it?", "qSentId": 651}, {"answer": "Well, he's got to have to come down the lane.", "docId": "120813pmt", "aSentId": 662, "question": "How are you going to feel when he comes to the Garden in a Houston shirt?", "qSentId": 661}, {"answer": "You just finished doing the Mike Tyson Show, which I saw a fledgling version of it in Vegas.", "docId": "120813pmt", "aSentId": 665, "question": "Hey, I'm not -- no blood, no foul, right?", "qSentId": 664}]